





Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects | Work Authorization

Summary

Jump to Section

Having 10 months of professional experience in the programming on Java, Linux and Database.

Proficient in Java, linux

Well acquainted with Software Development Life Cycle.

Experience involves requirements gathering, development, deployment and maintenance.

Effective in working independently and collaboratively in teams.

Work Experience

Sears IT & Management Services India as Intern

Sep 2019 to Jul 2020

worked on java linux and MySQL

Sears IT & Management Services India as Intern

Sep 2019 to Jun 2020

worked on java Linux mysql

Sears IT & Management Services India as Intern

Sep 2019 to Jun 2020

worked on java Linux mysql

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Electronics and Telecommunication) from Babasaheb Ambedkar Marathwada University in 2019

PG: Other (other) in 0

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: linked in MySQL essential training Linux certification on LinkedIn

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Java, Linux, Python	
MySQL	

1

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld. Eclipse, putty, VS code

Mcrosoft,Linux

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓
hindi	Expert	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

Projects

Project Title: Dynamic Pricing Client: Sears IT & Management Services India Nature of Employment: Full Time

Project Details: worked on prices of item's or products

Duration: Sep 2019 - Jun 2020 Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization US Work Status: Need H1 Visa

Category: General

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.